Have you got it yet?
拿到东西没有
Told you I'd call you as soon as I have everything.
我说过都到手后就会通知你
I'm paying you a lot of money, Collette.
我可是花了重金雇佣你 科勒特
And if you could've gotten
如果你能从别处
the detailed specs of a facility this secure
弄到这间机构的详细资料
from someone else, you would've.
你早就那么做了
CTU is no longer an obstacle.
已经扫清了CTU这块绊脚石了
This facility has been contaminated with Sentox VX-1 nerve gas.
大厦已被Sentox VX-1型神经毒气污染
Everybody
所有人
leave the situation room. Move! Now!
撤离局势研究室 快
Seal it.
封上
Lynn, it's Jack.
林 我是杰克
We found a computer interrupt in the AC control unit.
通风系统控制室中 有一台计算机无法访问
Now if we can shut that down in the next few minutes, we can stop the gas
如果能在几分钟内关闭干扰程序 就可以阻止毒气
from permeating the safe zones.
蔓延到安全地带
The problem is you're the only person close enough to get to it.
问题是只有你离那里最近
Lynn, the truth is if I could get there,
林 说实话 如果我离得近
I would do this myself, but I'm not close enough.
我会亲自去 但我离得远了
And I'm going to have to ask you to do it without any protection.
你只能在没有 保护措施的情况下去修复系统
He did it.
他做到了
CTU is protecting this city.
CTU负责保卫这座城市
Are you saying they're no longer capable of doing that?
你意思是他们已经不能履行职责了?
I'm saying they've been seriously compromised here.
我是说他们自身难保
We've got terrorists with nerve gas canisters out there.
持有神经毒气罐的恐怖份子 仍旧逍遥法外
Who is going to stop them?
谁来阻止他们
Mr. President, I suggest an emergency restructuring.
总统先生 我建议进行紧急重组
CTU is no longer an operational entity.
CTU已经无法正常运作
It's a building with workers who will report to us.
CTU只是一幢有人为我们工作的大楼而已
I can see no other option right now
我们没有其他选择
but to impose marshal law on the city of Los Angeles.
除了在洛杉矶实施戒严以外
What I will not do
我不会
is stand by and watch Hal Gardner use you
袖手旁观看着哈尔・加德纳尔
to promote his own agenda.
利用你来达成他自己的野心
You killed my wife Michelle Dessler this morning.
你今早害死了我的妻子 米歇尔・戴斯勒
She was my life.
她是我的生命
And you took her.
而你夺走了她
My God, he's got a gun.
他有枪
You can't do this.
别这样
We have to get him talking.
我们得让他招供
He's our only lead to Bierko and the Sentox gas canisters.
他是我们找到比耶科 和余下毒气罐的唯一线索
You've had your chance.
给过你机会了
He's mine now.
他现在归我了
Tony!
托尼
The following takes place between 8Pm and 9Pm.
以下是发生于夜晚8点至9点之间的故事
Jack, I am so sorry.
杰克 我很遗憾
Security find Henderson yet? No, he got
保安抓到亨德森没有
out of the building before the lockdown.
没有 他在封锁前就逃走了
An external cam got a shot of him as he was leaving.
外部摄象机抓拍到了一个 他离开时的画面
And the car that he was using was found a block away.
在一个街区以外 发现了他逃跑时所使用的车
But I think that we might've got what we needed from him.
可我想我们已经取得了 从他那里得来的情报
What are you talking about?
什么意思
Chloe was able to decrypt a file from his computer.
科洛伊解密了 他的计算机上的一个文件
She got a name of someone connected to Bierko.
她找到了一个与比耶科有关的人
Who's Collette Stenger?
这个科勒特・斯登格是谁
She's an international intelligence broker.
她是一名国际情报经济人
State secrets, intellectual property.
国家秘密 知识产权
What's her connection to Bierko?
她和比耶科有什么联系
Interpol claims that she and Bierko
国际刑警声称她和比耶科
met at least twice over the last eight months.
在过去的8个月内至少见过两次面
And we think she helped broker the deal.
通过她的帮助达成交易的
Is she still in Los Angeles?
她还在洛杉矶
She gave a name of a hotel to customs.
她给了海关一个酒店的地址
But nothing's to say that she's actually there.
但不能保证她真在那里
Curtis is prepping a tactical team to try to bring her in.
柯蒂斯在准备外勤组 把她抓来
Okay. Good work.
好 干得好
Manning.
曼宁
Curtis, it's Jack.
柯蒂斯 我是杰克
When is the tac team leaving?
你们什么时候出发
- Right now. - I'm going with you.
- 马上  - 我和你一起去
All right.
好
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen,
女士们先生们 晚上好
member of the press corps...
记者团的成员...
Just so you're aware, there will be no Q&A
请各位注意 总统在发表声明后
following the president's statement.
不会有问答时间
But you can submit questions to my office...
你们有问题可以向我的办公室提出...
You're having second thoughts?
你犹豫了
Putting soldiers on the streets of L.A.,
把士兵安置在洛杉矶大街上
this will not be a popular announcement.
这次讲话可不会受欢迎
Maybe not.
也许吧
But it's the right move.
但这是正确的决定
Hal, would you excuse us, please?
哈尔 请让我和他单独说句话
Mrs. Logan, the president's about to go on the air.
洛根夫人 全国都等着总统呢
I'll be brief.
就几句话
I would like a moment alone with my husband.
我想和丈夫单独呆一下
I've made up my mind, Martha.
玛莎 我已经下定决心了
I'm not debating this anymore.
无须多言
Just listen, listen please.
你听就可以了
Mike Novick spoke to someone at CTU.
麦克・诺维克和CTU的人 刚通完电话
They think they have a lead on this man Bierko.
他们认为已找到了 与比耶科有关的线索
They think they may find him before he launches another attack.
并可以在他发动下次袭击前找到他
CTU was just hit. 40% of their people are either dead or unable to work.
CTU刚遭到袭击 四成人员非死即伤
To think that they would be able
认为他们会阻止这次袭击
to stop this attack, that's just wishful thinking.
只是一相情愿的想法罢了
Maybe not.
也许并不是
Bringing the military in is the best way to maintain order.
使用军队是维持秩序的最佳方案
The Vice President's right about that.
副总统这么做是对的
Of course he is.
他那么做当然对
What's that mean?
什么意思
Hasn't it ever occurred to you
你难道没想过
that he proposed this whole thing to set you up for a fall?
他建议你这么做 就是为了让你早点下台
So he gets the nomination next year.
这样明年他就可以获得总统提名
That's insane.
这是不可能的
Hal's only motivation is what's best for the country.
哈尔只是为国家的利益着想
There's going to be fallout.
这样做会有意想不到的后果
Hal knows it.
哈尔清楚这一点
And you know it.
你也清楚
Mr.President.
总统先生
I have to go.
时间到了
Charles...
查尔斯...
Ladies and gentlemen,
各位
the President of the United States.
美利坚合众国总统
As you all know, America has been hit today
众所周知 今天美国遭到
by a series of terrorist strikes,
一系列恐怖袭击
beginning with the assassination of former President David Palmer
前任总统大卫・帕默遭刺杀...
and the murder of innocent Americans at Ontario Airport,
无辜的美国平民 在安大略机场遇害
followed by the attempted assassination of Russian President Yuri Suvarov.
随后俄罗斯总统 尤里・苏沃洛夫又遇袭
These events are being orchestrated
这些事件都是由
by terrorists operating within our borders.
在我国境内的恐怖份子精心策划的
Our most recent intelligence suggests
我们最新的情报表明
that they will strike again and soon.
他们很快会发动新一轮袭击
I can and will do my sworn duty
我将尽我宣誓时的义务
to ensure the safety of the American people.
来确保美国民众的安全
Therefore I am issuing an executive order
因此 我要发布一条行政命令
imposing a curfew on all civilians
对洛杉矶区域内的平民
in the Los Angeles metropolitan area.
实行强制宵禁
This curfew will be effective immediately
这次宵禁将立即生效
and will be enforced by the military.
并由军队强制执行
As disruptive and distasteful as I know this is for many of you,
我知道有许多人会反感或不满
I would ask that you remember that we are at war.
但我要提醒各位 我们正处于战争状态
Bracing ourselves against future attacks...
打起精神 准备抗击未来的袭击
D.O.D. is asking for a list of our casualties.
国防部在要我们的伤亡名单
I don't want any names released
在通知家属之前
until the next of kin have been notified.
不要发表任何姓名
Let me know when that happens.
有什么情况通知我
This place is a sinking ship.
这地方像艘幽灵船
We should be taking over now
我们应该现在就接手
not going through the charade of an assessment.
不用经过一系列的评估
Until we're ready to transition
在我们准备过渡之前
we need everyone here functioning.
需要调动每一个人
Once the remaining canisters of nerve gas have been found
一旦找到剩余的毒气罐
and the terrorists captured,
逮到恐怖份子以后
then we'll assume full control.
我们就全面控制这里
Karen.
凯伦
Hello, Bill.
你好 比尔
Bill Buchanan, Miles Papazian from my office.
比尔・布坎南 我部门的麦尔斯・帕帕齐安
I appreciate your coming, but that wasn't necessary.
感谢你们前来 但没有必要
We just need to replace some key personnel.
我们只需要替换一些主要员工
We're all sorry about the loss of lives here,
对于这里的死难者我们深表遗憾
but the White House feels you may need more than that.
但白宫认为你们 可能需要更多的协助
They want an assessment
上头需要一份国土安全部如何
of how Homeland may best assist CTU.
可以全力协助CTU的评估报告
I'll brief you in my office.
到我办公室向你汇报
Fine.
好
Miles, familiarize yourself with the networks
麦尔斯 熟悉一下网络
and then start the survey.
然后开始审查
Let's go.
走吧
Upstairs.
去楼上
Chloe O'Brian?
科洛伊・奥布赖恩
Who are you?
你哪位?
Homeland Security.
国土安全部的人
I asked your name, not who you work for.
我问的是你的名字 不是你工作的单位
I need a vacant station set up.
我需要一处闲置的工作站
I'm kind of busy right now.
你没看我忙着呢
I'm seeing Edgar Stiles listed on my report as a casualty.
据报告显示 埃德加・斯特尔斯出现在阵亡名单内
Is that right?
对吗
Yeah.
是的
Then his station should be available.I'll set up over there.
那他的工作站就是空的 我就在那里办公吧
I'll be reinstalling operating protocols for everyone in your group,
我会为你们的团队的每个人 重新安装操作协议
so I'll need your keycard.
所以要用一下你的钥匙卡
No.
不行
I'm sorry?
什么
You can't have my keycard.
我的钥匙卡不能给你
We're here with a priority admin directive.
我们有优先管理权
You can confirm that with your supervisor on your own time.
你自己可以 到你的上级那里证实一下
We're live in Los Angeles, where just a few minutes ago,
我们在洛杉矶现场为您报道
Army units stationed in L.A. County
几分钟前 洛杉矶的驻军
began moving in force across city limits.
开始成群向城市周边进发
This is the first time a military presence of this scale
这是第一次在大都市区域
has been activated in a major metropolitan area.
起用如此大规模的军队
While White House officials have stopped short
这仅在白宫官员
of officially declaring full-scale martial law...
正式宣布实施全面戒严后不久
Where are you going?
你要去哪里
I just need some fresh air.
出去透口气
These mobile Army divisions were activated
总统在新闻发布会上
in which he declared an enforced curfew.
这些机动部队便全面启动
shortly after the President's press conference
宣布实施强制宵禁不久
I do not trust him.
我可信不过他
Ma'am?
夫人
The Vice President.
副总统
This is Aaron Pierce.
我是艾伦・皮尔斯
Aaron,
艾伦
it's Wayne Palmer.
我是韦恩・帕默
Sir, I am so sorry about President Palmer,
先生 对于帕默总统遭遇我很遗憾
more sorry than I can describe.
悲痛之情我无法言表
Aaron, I know how close you were to my brother.
艾伦 我知道你对我兄长情深意重
You must have known he felt the same way about you.
你要知道他也是如此
Thank you for saying that.
谢谢你这么说
Actually, Aaron, he's the reason I'm calling.
事实上 他也是我打电话的原因
There's something from my brother I need to give you personally.
我哥有些东西 我要亲自给你
I should be there within the hour.
我1小时内就会到
You're coming here?
你要到这里来
Yeah, I know it sounds impulsive, Aaron.
我知道听起来很冲动
There's a curfew in effect, sir.
在实行宵禁呢 先生
I know, I know. I left before it was declared.
我知道 我在宣布宵禁前就出发了
If I may say so, this is an odd request.
恕我直言 这是一个奇怪的要求
Aaron, my brother trusted you with his life.
艾伦 我哥用他的生命信任你
I am asking you to trust me.
我请求你同样的相信我
All right.
好吧
I'd also appreciate it if you would keep this between us.
这事最好只有你我知道
I'm hoping there's somewhere we can meet discreetly.
我希望可以找个安全的地方见面
I'll find a place.
交给我吧
Thank you, Aaron.
谢谢 艾伦
I'll call you when I'm close.
我快到的时候 会给你打电话
The effects of this action will no doubt
毫无疑问 这次行动的影响将席卷全国
ripple across the country, as other cities begin to take note.
其他城市已经开始注意这一点
So while legislators debate
所以当立法委员
the legality of President Logan's action,
在讨论总统举措的合法性的时候
martial law is already a fact...
戒严法已经...
Mike, turn it off.
麦克 关了它
"Debate the legality of President Logan's action."
"讨论总统举措的合法性"
Did you hear that? They're talking about this like it's an illegal action.
你听到了吗 他们把这事当作非法行动来谈论
Don't worry, Mr. President.
不必担心 总统先生
I'm in control of the situation.
局势在我的掌控之下
Our legal people are working on it right now.
我们的法律班子正在研究对策
Do we have anything more from CTU?
CTU那边还有消息?
They're still following up on this Bierko lead.
他们依旧在追查比耶科这条线索
As soon as they have something to report,we'll be the first to hear.
他们一有新发现 我们会首先知道
Give me details of the current threat assessment.
说一下当前威胁评估的具体内容
There's a high probability that Bierko is planning an attack
比耶科很有可能在策划一次
on a much larger scale than anything we've seen today.
比我们今天所见到的更大规模的袭击
That's why he targeted CTU.
这就是他袭击CTU的原因
to cripple our ability to stop him.
来削弱我们阻止他的能力
And the question is: Was he successful?
问题是 他成功没有呢?
When you look at the numbers,
当你看到数字的时候
you were harder hit than you thought, Bill.
事实要比想象的更严重
We're still functioning.
我们还在运作
Maybe not at a 100%,
也许不是百分百运作
but when you install the people I've asked for...
但当你安置好我们需要的人...
we'll be back to fighting strength.
我们就会恢复正常
Have you made any progress finding Bierko?
在搜索比耶科上有任何进展么
We've identified a woman we believe might lead us to him.
我们已经确认一个女子 她可能会帮我们找到他
Collette Stenger.
科勒特・斯登格
We've just sent a tac team to bring her in.
我们刚派了一个外勤组实施抓捕
Good.
好
I enjoy watching you get dressed
我喜欢看你穿衣服...
almost as much as I enjoy watching you get undressed.
正如我喜欢看你脱衣服一样
You should get dressed yourself and send the bags down.
你该起来穿衣服 去把袋子送下去了
This deal you're working on,
你现在做的这笔买卖
I hope you're getting a lot of money for it.
能赚很多钱吧
I never talk about my business, you know that.
我从不谈公事 这你是知道的
I know...
不过...
but Maria called about this villa in Positano.
玛利亚从波西塔诺打来电话 谈这座别墅的事
She said when you see it, you'll love it.
她说你看到后肯定会喜欢
We'll call her later.
晚些时候再给她打电话
I'll see you at the airport, okay? In 45 minutes.
45分钟后 机场见
I'll be there.
好的
Yes.
讲
I'm on my way.
我上路了
And you have everything I asked for?
我要的东西都拿到了吧
Of course.
当然
Good.
好
Do you have the money?
钱准备好没有
As soon as I verify the merchandise
等我验过货以后
I'll have it transferred to your account.
就汇到你的帐户上
I'll be there soon.
我很快就到
Does she have the schematics and the access codes?
她有蓝图和验证码?
Yes.
有
Everything we need.
我们需要的一切东西都有
The Distribution Center is a difficult target.
货物储运中心是个难点
It would be much easier to hit a less secure location.
如果打击一个 防范疏松的地方会更容易些
No, Mikhail,
不 米哈伊尔
this is the place.
就是这里
Release the Sentox here...
在这里释放毒气
and 200,000 people die.
弄死20万人
And we need a second satellite repositioned as soon as possible.
让卫星尽快重新定位
- Good. - Thank you.
- 好的  - 谢谢
I saw a request for proficiency evaluations
我在我的副窗口上看到了一份
for all CTU personnel on my secondary screen.
CTU员工的技能评估申请
That's a formality. The fact is, we don't have time for evaluations right now.
例行公事而已 我们没有时间搞什么评估
Then why was it put in the pipeline?
既然如此为什么还有这个申请
Like I said, it's a formality.
正如我所说的一样 是例行公事
You're here to shut this place down, aren't you?
你是来关闭这里的 对不
And the evaluations will be filled in later as a matter of protocol.
稍后将作为例行程序进行评估审查
I told you before, the White House...
我和你说过 白宫
I know what you told me before.
我记得你和我说过什么
Now tell me the truth.
告诉我实情
The truth is, CTU is being absorbed by Homeland.
事实是CTU已被国土安全部所接管
Which means, from now on, every operational decision needs to go through me.
就是说 从现在开始 每项行动决策都要请示我
Bill, what did you expect?
比尔 你认为呢
You've been infiltrated.
敌人乘虚而入
56 of your peoplehave been killed.The others are demoralized...
你们有56人被害 剩下的人则是意志消沉
They're not demoralized,they're angry!
他们不是意志消沉 而是怒不可遏
They want to fight back.
他们要奋力反击
They're willing to lay down their lives.Some already have...
为此 有些人已经献出自己的生命
It's done, Bill.
都结束了 比尔
The decision's been made.
这是已经决定的事
And I know neither one of us wants
我很清楚 你我都不愿意
this transition to interfere with ongoing protocol,
让这次过渡有碍规章制度
so let's just keep it between us.
所以这事最好只有你我知道
At least until this crisis plays out.
至少等到这场危机结束
Bill?
比尔
Homeland is being overly aggressive with their survey.
国土安全部的审查态度异常强硬
What is going on?
出了什么事
Nothing.
没什么事
It's just a formality.They'll be gone as soon as they finish their evaluation.
例行公事而已 评估完成后 他们就走
Where are we on the military mobilization?
军队的调动上进展如何
Martial law is in effect in nine of the 15 L.A.districts.
洛杉矶15个区内有9区实施戒严
I'm setting up checkpoints for the rest of the county now.
我正在统计余下部分的检查站
I hope the president's doing the right thing.
希望总统这么做是对的
Alpha Team,
A组
we're approaching Collette Stenger's apartment
我们正接近科勒特・斯登格的房间
and we're ready to move.Are you in position?
我们准备行动了 你们就位没有
Affirmative. We've got the lobby covered.
是的 我们已经控制大厅
Copy.
收到
I think she went for the roof. Cover the stairs.
我想她去楼顶了 守住楼梯
Let's go.
我们走
We're going up top.
去楼顶
Drop the gun!
把枪放下
Stand down or he dies!
退后 不然他死定了
I said stand down!
我说了退后
Our people are all around you.
我们的人都把你包围了
They will drop you before you could pull that trigger.
在你扣动扳机前就会放倒你
Put the gun down!
放下枪
What do you mean your "people?" Who are you?
什么叫"你们的人" 你们是什么人
Counter Terrorist Unit, Los Angeles.
洛杉矶反恐组
Show me identification.
给我看证件
I'm with the German Federal Intelligence Service.
我是德国情报局的人
My name's Theo Stoller.
我叫西奥・斯托勒
What are you doing in this country?
你来这个国家做什么
I'm here on special assignment...
执行一项特别任务
by agreement between our governments.
经过双方政府同意的
Now you can get the hell out of here before you destroy my cover.
在你们使我的身份暴露之前 赶快离开这里
That's not going to happen.
不行
O'Brian.
奥布赖恩
Chloe, it's Jack.
科洛伊 我是杰克
I want you to check on a foreign agent on the SA list.
帮我在SA名单上查询一名外籍特工
"Theo Stoller."
西奥・斯托勒
Okay.
好
Got it: "Theo Stoller,
找到了 西奥・斯托勒
height, 5'll", brown hair, brown eyes."
身高5英尺10英寸 棕色头发和眼睛
He's a German operative,but trained in England at MI-6.
是一名受训于英格兰军情六处的德国刑警
There's even contact information: cell phone...
还有联系资料 手机号码 家庭地址
That's all right, Chloe.That's enough, thanks.
科洛伊 够了 谢谢
I told you, you have to get out of here now.
我已经说过了 你们得马上离开这里
We can't do that.
不行
You were with Collette Stenger.
你和科勒特・斯登格在一起
We need her to help us find Vladimir Bierko.
她是我们抓捕弗拉迪米尔・比耶科的线索
I don't know him.
我不认识他
Bierko's responsible for the terrorist attacks
比耶科对今天早些时候
that took place in the city earlier today.
发生在市内的恐怖袭击负有责任
He's preparing to mount another one as we speak.
此时他正准备发动另一次袭击
Collette Stenger is the only way we can find him.
科勒特・斯登格 是我们找到他的唯一线索
Where is she?
她在哪里
I can't help you.
我帮不了你
Why not?
为什么
Giving you Collette jeopardizes my operation.
把科勒特交给你 将破坏我们的行动
What operation?
什么行动
I've been undercover for the last six months
在过去的6个月中我作为卧底
gathering intel on Collette's clientele.
来搜集柯登格客户的情报
We've identified cells in three countries,
我们已在三个国家内 确认了相关恐怖组织
but she's connected to a dozen more.
但与她有联系的还有一打多
She's too valuable to give up.
她太有价值了 不能拱手相让
If we don't find Bierko
如果我们找不到比耶科
hundreds of thousands of innocent people will die here today.
今天就会有成千上万无辜的人死掉
That is more important than your preemptive operation.
这要比你们先入为主的行动 更为重要
It's not a question of importance,
这不是轻重缓急的问题
it's a question of different agendas.
而是动机和出发点的问题
Your job is to save American lives.
你的职责是挽救美国人的性命
Mine to save German lives.
我的职责是挽救德国人的生命
You're asking me to betray my duty to my country.
你意思让我背叛 我的国家赋予我的使命
Ask yourself what you would do in my position.
你自问一下 如果你是我会怎么做
You better start asking yourself what you would do in mine.
你最好先问你自己 换作你是我会怎么做
Now, let's go.
走
I'm here by permission of your government,you can't touch me.
我来这里是得到你们政府的许可的 别碰我
Right.We'll see about that.
好 我们走着瞧吧
Well, make sure that your superior
最好让你的上级知道
understands that if this attack happens,
如果发生了袭击
my government will hold your country accountable.
我们的政府会拿贵国试问
Jack, it's Buchanan.Audrey will be joining us momentarily.
杰克 我是布坎南 奥黛丽马上就来
You're also on the line with Karen Hayes from Homeland Security.
这里还有国土安全部的凯伦・海因斯
She's been providing support to CTU
她一直在为CTU提供帮助
and she's also been in contact with the White House.
并与白宫有联系
Did President Logan get in touch with the German Chancellor?
洛根总统与德国总理联系上了吗
He's tried the chancellor's unreachable for another hour.
他试过了 但一小时后才能联系到总理
We don't have another hour.
我们哪来的一小时
They're stalling, there's nothing we can do about that.
他们在推托 我们无能为力
Jack, this is Audrey.I was just speaking with German Intelligence.
杰克 我是奥黛丽 我刚与德国情报局通过电话
They're refusing to order their agent to cooperate with us.
对方拒绝命令他们的特工 和我们合作
Maybe you can get a deal with him.
也许你能和他谈一下条件
Okay, I'll talk to Stoller again.
好吧 我再和斯托勒谈谈
Good. Call me if you get him to change his mind.
能让他改变主意就通知我
Yeah.
恩
Curtis?
柯蒂斯
Let me have a moment with him alone.
让我和他单独呆会
Jack, what are you doing?
杰克 你要干什么
It's all right.
放心吧
All right.
好嘛
Your intelligence service denied our request for cooperation.
你们的情报局回绝了 我们想合作的请求
So has your government.
你们的政府也是如此
I'm not surprised.
没什么奇怪的
Collette Stenger is a golden goose.
科勒特・斯登格是一个金元宝
There's no upside in giving her up.
我们没理由会放弃她
Maybe I could provide you with one.
也许我可以给你一个理由
Meaning?
什么意思
I will give you something that is more valuable than Collette Stenger.
我会给你某些 比科勒特・斯登格更宝贵的东西
It's hard to know what that might be.
我猜不出是什么
Our roster of all known terror suspects
我们在全球所掌握的 已知恐怖份子的名单
working around the world, our WET list.
一份WET(西欧恐怖份子)名单
As allies, we've requested this WET list many times before.
作为盟国 在此之前我们已多次索取这份名单
But the NSA has always said,giving us the list would jeopardize their operations.
但国土安全部却总是声称 如果提供名单就会破坏行动
It will.
确实如此
I don't work for the NSA, I don't work for CTU.
我不为国土安全部或CTU效力
This is personal.And right now, you're not giving me another choice.
这是我个人提供的条件 你现在也没给我选择的余地
All right.
好
I'll give you Collette
我用科勒特...
in exchange for the WET list.
来换取名单
Good.
合作愉快
Let's see what we can do.
我看一下该怎么做
Agent Bauer.
鲍尔探员
I'm aware of several names that should be on that list.
我知道有几个人的名字 应该在那份名单上
Don't try and pass me a fake.
别拿伪造的打发我
O'Brian.
奥布赖恩
Chloe, it's Jack.
科洛伊 我是杰克
Do we still have a back door into NSA's secured mainframe?
我们还可以从后门进入 国土安全部的安全主机不?
I can't really talk right now, Jack.
现在说话不方便 杰克
Okay, fine. Then, listen.
好 那就听我说
I need you to log on to their server
立即进入他们的服务器
download the WET list, and send it to my PDA immediately.
下载WET名单 然后传到我的PDA上
Why?
为什么
The WET list is what we're gonna have to pay to get Collette Stenger.
WET名单是我们抓到 科勒特・斯登格的交换条件
Jack, that list is as top secret as it gets.
杰克 名单机密程度是相当高的
Homeland Security sent a team over here.
国土安全部派了一组人到这里来
You're gonna have to clear it with them.
你必须得到他们的许可
We can't afford to take the chance of them saying no.
我们不能冒险被他们拒绝
I'm not saying I won't do it without their approval.
不是我不想帮你
I'm saying I can't.
而是我帮不了你
They took my keycard.
他们拿走了我的钥匙卡
I can't get into the NSA mainframe without it.
没有它 我无法进入国土安全部的主机
Just do what you have to.It's our only way to get Bierko.
想方设法吧 这是我们追查到比耶科的唯一途径
Fine. I'll call you back.
好吧 我一会再打给你
Excuse me, Miles.
打扰一下 麦尔斯
My God!
我的天
What is the matter with you?
你长眼睛干嘛用的?
Sorry.
抱歉
What's wrong with you?
你可真是的
I'll pay for the dry cleaning.
我付你干洗费
Yeah?
喂
Jack, I got on the NSA server.
杰克 我进入国土安全部的服务器了
Did you get the file?
找到那份文件了吗
Not yet. They put an extra layer of authentication in place.
还没有 他们添加了额外的认证
Can you get around it?
绕得开不
Hold on.
稍等
Okay, I got it.
好 找到了
I hope you know what you're doing.
希望你知道自己在做什么
I'm uploading it now.
我现在就传给你
Thanks.
谢了
I got it.
到手了
Well, that appears legitimate.
看来是真的
It is.
是真的
Give me back the memory card.
记忆卡还我
You can't upload the WET list to your people
抓到她之前
until I have Collette Stenger in custody.
不能把WET名单给你们
Well, fair enough.
很公平
We have to go now.
我们得快点
I'm supposed to meet her at the Van Nuys airport in less than 20 minutes.
我和她约好20分钟内 在范内斯机场见面
What kind of a car is she driving?
她开的是什么车
I don't know.I'm supposed to park in car Lot C and wait for her.
不清楚 我约好在C停车场等她
She'll probably recon the area before she makes contact.
在和我见面前 她可能会先侦察一下那附近
She's, uh, cautious by habit.
她习惯了小心谨慎
Curtis, we're on the move  Van Nuys Airport.
柯蒂斯 我们这就出发
We'll give you the details when we're on the way.
去范奈司机场 路上再详细布置
When you receive the funds,
收到钱后
transfer them immediately into the Caymans account.
立即转到开曼的帐户上
In Euros.
换成欧元
My bank is ready to accept the transfer.
银行准备好接收汇款了
The file is encrypted.
文件被加密了
What is the decryption key?
说解码口令
Transfer the funds.
汇款
It's been sent.
汇出去了
Thank you.E-mail me confirmation of the transfer.
谢谢 发给我确认汇款的邮件
The decryption key is Charlie Alpha Three Nine Alpha.
密钥是C-A-3-9-A
It worked. This is what you wanted.
是真的 这正是你想要的
Of course it is.
当然是
Until next time, gentlemen.
下次见 先生们
Are the men ready?
人都准备好没有
Yes.
好了
Torch this place.We're moving out.
把这地方烧了 我们出发
Governor, I'm not trying to co-opt your authority,
州长 我不是想篡夺你的权利
but we are in the middle of a crisis here.
但我们身处危机之中
Now, you can either transmit my orders word for word to the National Guard
你可以把我的命令 下达给国民警卫队
or I can federalize them,and give them my orders directly
或是我让他们归联邦管辖 我来直接下令
your choice.
你决定
Excellent.
好极了
Thank you, Governor.I look forward to your croperation.
谢谢你 州长 期待与你合作
Sir, we have a situation at one of the roadblocks
先生 有一处路障出了些状况
that the region three commander needs your call on.
3区指挥官要向您请示一下
Tell me.
说吧
Wayne Palmer is insisting he be let through one of our roadblocks.
韦恩・帕默坚持 他有权通过那道路障
He claims he still has his clearance and that he's on official business.
他声称他仍旧获准通过那里 并有公事在身
And where exactly is that?
到底是什么地方
He was stopped trying to get on the access road coming towards the retreat.
他在来戴维营的路上被拦下的
He's on his way here? To do what?
他来这里做什么
He wouldn't give the officer in charge of the roadblock any information.
他不愿首先透漏任何信息
What should I tell the roadblock, sir?
我该和当值的军官怎么说 先生
Captain, all I'm asking you to do is call and confirm
上尉 我只请你打个电话
I have a grade two clearance, that's it.
确认我有二级许可 仅此而已
Sir, regardless of your clearance authorization to let you through
先生 不管你是否有许可
must come down through the appropriate chain of command.
都必须得到有关上级的批准
And just who would that be, huh, Captain?
谁的批准 上尉
Who's in charge of the military's role in this?
在这里军事上谁负责
Riggs.
里格斯
Understood.
明白
Thank you, sir.
谢谢 先生
You can go on through now, sir.
你现在可以通过了 先生
Let him through.
让他过去
Thank you, Captain.
谢谢 上尉
All teams are in position, Jack.
各组已就位 杰克
No one moves in until I confirm that it's her.
在我确认是她之前 不要擅自行动
Copy that.
收到
Collette won't show herself if she senses anything's wrong.
科勒特如果觉察到异样 就不会现身
Make sure he stays hidden.
确保让他隐蔽好
Don't worry. He will.
别担心 他会的
What will happen to her?
她会有什么下场
To Collette.
对科勒特来说
I don't know yet. Why?
不知道 为什么这么问
Uh, just curious.
好奇而已
You've been in my situation?
你有过和我一样的经历么
I've been undercover for long stretches of time, yeah.
我做过长时间的卧底
And been involved with a woman during that time?
在那段时间里和女人谈情说爱什么的?
There's no question we are doing what has to be done for our countries,
我们为国效力是天经地义的事情
but sometimes it's harder than others.
不过有时任务环境比较特殊
Chloe, could you join us in the Situation Room, please?
科洛伊 请和我去一下局势研究室
Sure.
好
What's going on?
出了什么事
Why don't you tell us, Ms. O'Brian?
你来告诉我们 奥布赖恩女士
I don't know.
我不知道
We've got you hacking into a top secret NSA archive.
我们发现你黑进了 国土安全部的一份高度机密档案
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你是什么意思
I pulled a mirrored archive of your web traffic.
我调出了你的网页流量镜像文件
Whatever you took from NSA was uploaded to Jack Bauer's remote node.
不管你从国土安全部得到了什么 你都传到了杰克・鲍尔的远程节点上
Ms. O'Brian, tell us exactly what document you passed to Jack Bauer.
奥布赖恩女士 你传给他的到底是什么文件
Chloe,
科洛伊
this is going to get much worse if you force me to have NSA run a back trace.
如果迫使我让国土安全部进行反追踪 事情会更严重
What is it?
是什么
Jack needed the WET List.
杰克需要WET名单
What?!
什么
Why on earth would you give him that?
到底为什么要给他名单
Theo Stoller wouldn't lead us to Collette Stenger without it.
没有名单 西奥・斯托勒 就不会带我们去找科勒特・斯登格
Chloe, giving that list to another intelligence agency could be disastrous.
科洛伊 把那份名单 给了其他情报局的后果不堪设想
Years of work could be rendered useless our own agents could be exposed.
几年的工作可能会前功尽弃 潜伏特工还可能会暴露身份
Jack needed it, okay?
杰克需要都不行?
No! No, it's not okay.
不 不行
And you expected us to give your agents a chance?
你还想让我们 给你们的特工一次机会
Get me Bauer.
给我接通鲍尔
Put it on speaker phone, or I'm getting out of this car.
切换成免提 不然我就下车
Fine.
好
This is Bauer.
鲍尔
Jack, it's Bill.
杰克 我是比尔
Karen Hayes is here, as well.
凯伦・海因斯也在这里
If you're with Theo Stoller,
如果你正和西奥・斯托勒在一起
get some place you can talk privately.
那就找个我们可以单独谈话的地方
I can't. We're in the middle of an operation.
不行 我们在执行任务
If I move I'll jeopardize our position.
如果移动就会暴露自己
Then you'll have to have this conversation in front of him.
那就只能当他的面谈了
Have you given him the WET List yet?
你给他WET名单了吗
Yes.
给了
Has he given it to German Intelligence?
他给德国情报局了吗
No.
没有
Then get it back. Now.
那就马上拿回来
I can't.
不行
If I do that, Stoller won't cooperate.
斯托勒不会答应的
And then we'll lose Collette Stenger.
我们也会失去科勒特・斯登格
Bill, will you explain this to her?
比尔 你给她解释一下好吗
It's not his decision.
这不是由他来决定的
Retrieve the WET list now
立即取回WET名单
or I will order Agent Manning and his team to do it.
否则我就派曼宁探员去拿
Right now, Collette Stenger is our only connection to Bierko.
当前 科勒特・斯登格 是我们找到比耶科的唯一线索
If you blow this operation, you will be responsible
如果你破坏了这次行动
for every life lost in his next attack.
你就要对他下次袭击的死难者负责
I don't like to be threatened, Mr. Bauer.
我可不喜欢被威胁 鲍尔先生
Ms. Hayes, that's not a threat, that's a fact.
海因斯女士 这不是威胁 而是事实
German Intelligence will move preemptively on people
德国情报局会先下手逮捕
that we have been watching for years.
我们已监控了几年的嫌犯
Our ability to prevent terrorist attacks will be severely threatened.
我们阻止恐怖活动的能力 将遭受严重威胁
Then that's a risk we'll have to take.
只能冒这个险
Right now, we have to deal with this situation.
我们要先着手眼前的事
It's not your call.
这不是你能决定的
It's not mine, either.
也不是我能决定的
We need authorization from the President.
我们需要总统的批准
Then get it.
那就去获得批准
Jack, one of our forward teams I.D.'d a woman fitting Stenger's description
杰克 我的手下发现 一名符合嫌犯特征的女子
driving a red Lexus making its second circuit around the lot.
正驾驶一辆红色凌志 环绕停车场第二圈行驶
This could be her.
可能就是她
We have a possible suspect approaching.
嫌犯可能正在靠近
Ms. Hayes, are you telling me that I have to abort this operation?
海因斯女士 我是否要取消这次行动
Yes or no?
是或否
Ms. Hayes, this is your call.
海因斯女士 你来决定
You don't know for certain that this woman will lead us to Bierko.
你并不能确定这个女人 会带我们抓到比耶科
No, not for certain.But, right now, she's our only lead.
对 不确定 但当前她是我们唯一的线索
Are you willing to take this chance?
你愿意冒这个险吗
You've left me no choice.Proceed.
你让我别无选择 继续执行任务
But you have severely compromised this situation
但如果你使事态加重
and I promise you there will be repercussions.
我保证你会受到处罚
Fine.
行
Are we all right?
我们没事了吧
We're fine.
没事
Red Lexus turning the corner.A hundred yards away and approaching.
红色凌志转弯 距离100码接近中
No one move until I give a go.
在我下令前 任何人不准行动
The red Lexus is parked.
红色凌志停下了
Move the center mirror, so that I can see the car.
调整后视镜 让我看到车
There.
好了
Now get her out of the car.
引她下车
I have a positive I.D.
嫌犯已确认
All teams move in.
各小组行动
All teams move, move, move! Let's go!
各小组行动 行动
Put your hands where I can see them!
把手放到我能看见的地方
Theo, get in the car, now.
西奥 快上车
What are you doing?
你要干什么
Let me see your hands!
把手举起来
Let me go.Now!
快放开我
Theo, get out of there.
西奥 让开
I'm sorry.
对不起
Theo, who are you?
西奥 你是什么人
Move! Letting him go.He's given us what we want!
走开 让他走 他已经给了我们想要的东西
Put your hands up!
把手举起来
Turn and face the car!
转身面向车
Put your hands on the roof!
把手放在车顶
Do it!
照做
Where is Bierko?
比耶科在哪儿
We know you're working with Bierko.
我们知道你和他打过交道
Where is he?
他在哪儿
Fine.
好
Take her back to staging.
把她带回营地
I want a team searching this car.
派一组人搜查这辆车
Take everything back to the staging area.
把所有东西都带回营地
Now!
快
It's Theo.
我是西奥
I'm en route to the hotel.
在回酒店的路上
Tell Heinrich I'm uploading something
告诉海因里希
he's been wanting for a long time.
我会上传一样他期待已久的东西
Stoller.
斯托勒
Theo, it's Jack.I'm sorry.
西奥 我是杰克 抱歉
I thought we had a deal.
我们有君子协定的
When this is over, I promise you,
这一切结束后
I will help you rebuild your investigation.I give you my word.
我保证会帮你重建调查 我向你保证
I had your word.
我有你的保证了
Now I know what it worth.
现在我知道它的价值了
What have you got?
有何线索
Nothing.
毫无头绪
She's covered her tracks.
她没留下线索
There's no sign
没有迹象表明
of what she sold to Bierko.
她卖给了比耶科什么东西
Come with me.
跟我来
Collette Stenger,
科勒特・斯登格
my name is Jack Bauer.
我是杰克・鲍尔
Who is Theo really?
西奥到底是什么人
German Intelligence.
德国情报局的人
Then he sold me for a price.
他出卖了我
German and American Intelligence don't work together often.
美德情报局不常合作的
Where is Bierko?
比耶科在哪儿
The fact is, I actually had feelings for Theo.
事实上 我对西奥是真心的
I never once suspected.He was very good.
我从没怀疑过他 他很了不起
I always thought that there
我总认为
were some things that you cannot fake.
有些东西是装不出来的
Bierko.
比耶科
Tell them to leave.
让他们走开
Jack?
杰克
It's all right.
没关系
Curtis, have your men move back
让你的人先撤出去
Just give us a second.
给我们一点时间
You've heard him.
你们听到了吧
Theo had a price.What's yours?
西奥给出了价钱 你的价钱是多少
I'm not for sale.
我不会出卖自己
Everyone is for sale.
每个人都会的
This isn't a game, lady.
这不是游戏 女士
We're running out of time.
我们没时间了
You better tell me what you want.
要什么条件你就说
All right.
好
Full immunity. No holdbacks.
完全赦免令 不许有保留条款
Signed by your president and transmitted to lawyers in Zurich and Tripoli.
你们的总统签署后发送给 我在苏黎士与黎波里的律师
But I can't tell you where Bierko is.
可我不能告诉你比耶科在哪里
Why not?
为什么
Because he's already gone.
因为他早就离开了
I met him at a safehouse,
我是在安全屋和他见面的
but he was already on his way to carry out the attack.
他已经去发动袭击了
What were you selling him?
你卖给他什么了
I don't know.
我不知道
What do you mean, you don't know?
你不知道是什么意思
I mean I don't know.
就是说我不知道
It was a schematic.
那只是一份蓝图
What kind of a schematic?
哪种类型的?
I'm paid to broker the information,
我是情报经纪人
not dwell on the details.
不会询问细节
I make it my firm policy.
这是我的原则
You expect me to believe that you acquired information
你真以为我会相信你获得了
for a terrorist group and you didn't know the specifics?
一分恐怖组织的情报却不知道细节
You can believe whatever you want.
你爱信不信
The fact is, I got the schematics from a source
实际上我从线人那里得来的蓝图
and they were digitally encrypted.
是经过电子加密的
That source can tell you what they mean.
那个线人可以告诉你 那些是什么蓝图
Give me immunity and I'll give you my source.
给我特赦令 我就给你线人
Those are my terms.
这就是我的条件
You haven't offered us very much.
你并没有多少资本来谈条件
I'll see what I can do.
我看看吧
Buchanan.
布坎南
Yeah, it's Jack.
我是杰克
She wants full immunity signed by the president.
她要求得到总统签署的完全赦免令
She claims that she doesn't know where Bierko is.
她声称并不知道比耶科在哪里
That she just brokered a deal for a set of schematics,and then delivered them.
她只负责给比耶科的团伙提供一份蓝图
She doesn't know what building they're for,
她不知道具体的建筑是什么
but she can provide us with the source of the schematics.
但可提供蓝图的源头来自何处
She doesn't know what she sold him?
她不知道卖给他什么东西
She said it was digitally encrypted.
她说蓝图经过电子加密
Do you believe her?
你相信她么
She's an independent contractor.
她是独立承包人
In her line of work, sometimes
做她们这一行的
what you don't know will save your life.
有时不知情反而能保住自身性命
Either way,
总之
if she's telling the truth, we don't have a lot of time.
如果她说的是实话 我们的时间就不多了
She said Bierko already left to set off his next attack.
她说比耶科已离开 去发动下次袭击
Miles, call Mike Novick, let's get this started.
麦尔斯 去给麦克・诺维克打电话 开始着手办这事
Jack,
杰克
this better work.
这么做最好有效果
And for the record, I don't like it.
记住 这种方式我不太喜欢
We've paid a steep price.
我们付出了高昂的代价
There'll be fallout on the WET List.
WET名单会产生意想不到的后果
No, there won't be.The fallout will be from German Intelligence.
不会的 只会对德国情报局有影响
I programmed the memory card to self-destruct.
我编程序使记忆卡自毁了
Why didn't you tell us this before?
为什么不早说
I told you, I was in the car with Stoller.
我说过当时我和斯托勒在车里
Get back to me as soon as this is done, we need to move fast.
事情办好后就通知我 动作要快
I think it's clear.
显而易见
CTU was hit,but we're still doing our job.
虽然CTU遭到袭击 但我们仍旧坚守岗位
I believe that's an argument to maintain our autonomy.
这就是我们可以自治的证据
Well, I'll withhold judgment on that.
我持保留意见
We're giving a free pass to a terrorist collaborator,
我们让通敌份子有了可乘之机
and I have yet to see what we're getting from it.
这样做的后果还没显现出来
Has the document been received in Tripoli as well?
黎波里也收到那份文件了吗
And it meets with your approval?
你同意了
So, there's no way that they can fail to live up to the terms?
就是说不会让他们钻了空子
Merci, Herve. Au revoir.
多谢 赫维 再见
The safehouse is a manufacturing facility at 12451 Saticoy Boulevard.
安全屋是在塞特考大街 12451号的一间制造厂
As for the data I sold to Bierko,it's something
至于我卖给比耶科的数据
that I received from a contact at the Department of Defense.
我是从国防部一个线人那里得到的
What's his name?
他是谁
Her name.
她叫
Audrey Raines.
奥黛丽・瑞恩斯
You are lying to me.
你在说谎
She sold me the information, Mr. Bauer.
是她卖给我的情报 鲍尔先生
Apparently she had a price.
显然这情报是有价提供的
Put her in the car.
把她押上车